[night animals calling]
[INSECTS BUZZING]
[fly buzzes]
[music begins]
♪ You and me ♪
♪ We used to be together ♪
♪ Every day together always ♪
♪ I really feel ♪
♪ That I'm losing
My best friend ♪
♪ I can't believe
This could be the end ♪
♪ It looks as though
You're letting go ♪
♪ And if it's real Well,
I don't want to know ♪
♪ Don't speak ♪
♪ I know
Just what you're saying ♪
♪ So please stop explaining ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ Don't speak ♪
♪ I know what you're thinking ♪
♪ I don't need your reasons ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ Our memories ♪
♪ Well, they can be inviting ♪
♪ But some are altogether
Mighty frightening ♪
♪ As we die, both you and I ♪
♪ With my head in my hands
I sit and cry ♪
♪ Don't speak ♪
♪ I know
Just what you're saying ♪
♪ So please stop explaining ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ Don't speak ♪
♪ I know what you're thinking ♪
♪ And I don't need
Your reasons ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ It's all ending ♪
♪ I gotta stop pretending
Who we are ♪
♪♪♪
[classical guitar playing]
♪ You and me ♪
♪ I can see us dying ♪
♪ Are we? ♪
♪ Don't speak ♪
♪ I know
Just what you're saying ♪
♪ So please stop explaining ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ Don't speak ♪
♪ I know what you're thinking ♪
♪ And I don't need
Your reasons ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ I know what you're saying ♪
♪ So please stop explaining ♪
♪ Don't speak ♪
♪ Oh, I know
What you're thinking ♪
♪ And I don't need
Your reasons ♪
♪ I know you're good
I know you're good ♪
♪ I know you're real good ♪
♪ Oh, la la la la ♪
♪ La la la la ♪
♪ Don't, don't ♪
♪ Oooh, oooh
Hush, hush darlin' ♪
♪ Hush, hush darlin' ♪
♪ Hush, hush ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ Hush, hush darlin' ♪
♪ Hush, hush, darlin' ♪
♪ Hush, hush ♪
♪ Don't tell me
'Cause it hurts ♪
♪ Oh, hush, hush, darlin' ♪
[night animals calling]